A Finding Aid to the Douglas Leigh Papers, 1903-1999, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Billboard Project Files, 1929-1997; Series 10; Archival Resource Key; (Box 1, 6, 14-25, BV 33; 5.0 linear feet)
  - Billboard Scrapbooks for Miscellaneous Products, 1933-1977; 10.4; Archival Resource Key
    Billboard Scrapbook 8 includes a photo of Joan Crawford; Billboard Scrapbook 9 includes a photo of cartoonist Otto Soglow; Billboard Scrapbook 10 includes photos of dancers Bill Robinson and the De Marcos; and Billboard Scrapbook 16 includes a photo of Sophia Loren.
    - Billboard Scrapbook 1 (see BV 33), 1933-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Billboard Scrapbooks 2-3 (Highlights of the Spectaculars)(see Box 15), 1934-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Billboard Scrapbooks 4-5 (Highlights of the Spectaculars)(see Box 16), 1945-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 6 (see also Box 14), 1934-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 62-64)
    - Billboard Scrapbooks 9-11 (see Box 18), 1938-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Billboard Scrapbooks 12-15 (see Box 19), 1950-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Billboard Scrapbooks 16-17 (see Box 20), 1962-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 18, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Billboard Scrapbook 19 (see Box 20), 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 1 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1933-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box BV 33)
    - Oversized Poster from Billboard Scrapbook 6, 1934-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 2 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1934-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 3 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1937-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 4 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1945-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 5 (Highlights of the Spectaculars), 1962-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 7, 1935-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 8, 1936-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 9, 1938-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 10, 1944-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 11, 1951-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 12, 1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 13, 1955-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 14, 1955-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 15, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 16, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 17, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 19, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 20, Camel Cigarettes, 1941-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Billboard Scrapbook 21, Camel Cigarettes, 1948-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Duplicate Photographs from Scrapbooks, circa 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Individual Billboard Product Files, 1936-1980; 10.5; Archival Resource Key
    Billboard Scrapbook 25 includes photographs of Broadway performers Joan McCracken, June Havoc, Bambi Linn, and the De Marcos; Wilson Whiskey Billboard Scrapbook 27 includes a photograph of Joan Crawford.
    - Aqua Net Hairspray Photographs, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Ballantine's Beer Photographs, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Black Horse Ale Photographs of Sign (see also Box 14), 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - BOAC Airlines Photographs, 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Bond Clothes Photographs (see also Box 14), 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Borden's Instant Coffee Photograph, ca. 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Braniff Airlines Photograph of Sign Installation, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Brim Freeze-Dried Coffee Photograph, ca. 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Bulova Watches Photographs, ca. 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Camel Cigarettes, Photographs, 1942-1951; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 79-80)
    - Canada Tourism, Photographs, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Chevrolet Automobiles, Photographs (see also Box 14), n.d.; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Cleopatra Movie Sign, Photographs of Executives Lighting Sign, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Coca-Cola, Photographs and World's Fair Material, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
    - Contac Cold Remedy, Photograph, ca. 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Eveready Batteries, Photographs (see Box 22), 1949-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Flamingo Foods, Photographs (see Box 14), 1951-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7-13)
    - General Electric Iron, Artwork for Billboard, 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Gordon's Gin/ Haig Scotch Whisky, Photographs, 1964-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
    - Grand Union Grocery Store, Photographs, ca. 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Hennessy Cognac, Photographs, 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Kool Cigarettes, Photograph, ca. 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Mattel Toys, Photographs, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Museum of Science and Industry, Photograph, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Nassau Tourism, Photographs, 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - N W Bank, Blueprints of Design for Sign, ca. 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Pepsi-Cola, Scripts for Animation of Pepsi EPOK in Tokyo, ca. 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24-25)
    - REM Cold Remedy, Photographs, 1945-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Rheingold Beer, Photographs, ca. 1940s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Salem Cigarettes, Notes and Photographs, ca. 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Savarin Coffee, Photograph, ca. 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Schaefer Beer, Photographs, 1945-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Scripto Pens, Photograph and Press Release, ca. 1940s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Sunbeam Vacuum Cleaner, Photographs, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - TDK Recording Tape, Photograph, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Teacher's Scotch Whisky, Photograph, ca. 1940s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Time, Life, Sports Illustrated Magazines, Loose Photographs from Billboard Scrapbook 26 (see Box 24), 1957-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - WABC Broadcasting, Photographs, ca. 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - War Bonds, Photographs, ca. 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Wilson Whiskey Loose Photographs, Scrapbook 27 (see Box 24), 1940-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Winston Cigarettes, Photographs, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - WNBC Broadcasting, Photograph, ca. 1940s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - WOR Broadcasting, Photographs, 1945-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Wrigley's Gum, Photograph of sign, ca. 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Oversized Photographs of Individual Product Signs, 1944-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Black Horse Ale
      Bond
      Clothes
      Chevrolet
      Flamingo
      Pepsi-Cola
    - Eveready Batteries, Billboard Scrapbook 22, 1949-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Pepsi-Cola, Billboard Scrapbook 23, 1955-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - REM, Billboard Scrapbook 24, 1945-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - REM, Billboard Scrapbook 25, 1945-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Time, Life, Sports Illustrated Magazines, Billboard Scrapbook 26, 1957-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Wilson Whiskey, Billboard Scrapbook 27, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Wilson Whiskey, Billboard Scrapbook 28, Aug-Nov 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Wilson Whiskey, Billboard Scrapbook 29, 1941-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Poster Project Files, 1943-1963; Series 11; Archival Resource Key; (Box 7-8, 14; 1.6 linear feet)
  This series consists of notes, reports, artwork, photographs, miscellaneous printed material, 4 scrapbooks, and individual product files that document the development of poster advertising projects, primarily those used on Railway Express Agency delivery trucks that would circulate the poster advertisements throughout urban areas. Individual product files typically contain photographs, notes, clippings, and other printed materials. Although scrapbooks have been consecutively numbered within this series, they either focus on multiple projects or are solely associated with one project and arranged with that project. There is also a file concerning the Shopping Center Network Semaphore Poster Display that involved the placement of hanging posters on light poles in shopping center parking lots.
  Poster project files are on reels 5845-5846.
  - Miscellaneous Notes, ca. 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Report: Consumer Recognition Study of Poster Advertising, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Report: A Comprehensive Study and Analysis of the REA Express Poster, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Report: Express Posters U.S.A., 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Artwork for a Poster by Walter Griffin (see also Box 14), 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous Press Releases, 1948, n.d.; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Poster Scrapbook 1, 1954-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - American Dairy Association Poster File, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Amoco Gasoline and Oil Poster File, ca. 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Amoco Gasoline and Oil, Poster Scrapbook 2, 1952-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Beeline Radio Stations Poster File, California and Nevada, ca. 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Black Label Beer, Stag Beer Poster File, ca. 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Blue Cross Poster File, ca. 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Camel Cigarettes, Poster Scrapbook 3, 1943-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Reel 56-60)
  - Camel Cigarettes, Poster Scrapbook 3, 1943-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1-8)
  - Camel Cigarettes, Poster Scrapbook 4, 1948-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9-23)
  - Chase and Sanborn Coffee Poster File, 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Flamingo Foods Poster File, 1951-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Fram Motor Oil Poster File, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Hudson Hornet Automobile Poster File, ca. 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Lux Soap Poster File, ca. 1940s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Museum of Science and Industry Poster File, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Red Cross Show, Madison Square Garden, Poster File, ca. 1940s-1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - REM Cold Remedy Poster File, ca. 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Salem Cigarettes Poster File, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Twenhoefel's Automobile Insurance Poster File, ca. 1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - U. S. Navy (WAVES) Poster File, ca. 1940s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - War Bonds Poster File, 1943-1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35-38)
  - Wearever Pens Poster File, ca. 1950s-1960s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Winston Cigarettes Poster File, 1958-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Shopping Center Network Semaphore Poster Display File, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 41-43)
  - Oversized Artwork for a Poster by Walter Griffin, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Dirigible Project Files, 1944-1954; Series 12; Archival Resource Key; (Box 8-11, 14, 26-28; 3.7 linear feet)
  This series consists of notes, reports, artwork, photographs, miscellaneous printed material, 12 scrapbooks, and individual product files that document the development of dirigible advertising projects involving both painted logos and networks of lights over the surface of the dirigible. Sequentially-timed lights caused dramatic animated effects against the night sky. Individual Product/Project Files are arranged alphabetically and typically contain photographs, scrapbooks, printed material, and scattered drawings. Leigh compiled scrapbooks of general information on dirigible advertising and for specific dirigible projects. General scrapbooks have been arranged by date and are interspersed throughout the series and specific project scrapbooks have been arranged with the appropriate product/project file.
  Dirigible project files are on reels 5846-5847.
  - Report: Surveys Measuring the Effectiveness of Dirigible Advertising, by Alfred Politz Research, Inc., 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 44-45)
  - Report: Blimps in Industry (Off-Shore Oil Operations), by Richard G. Kopff, Jan. 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Report: Study to Determine the Effectiveness of Sky Advertising, by Daniel Starch and Staff, May 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Drawings for Advertisements, ca. 1940s-1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 49-53)
  - Photographs of Advertisement Ideas, ca. 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Dirigibles, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Photographs of Leigh Sky Advertising Corp. Equipment, ca. 1940s-1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material, ca. 1940-1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 57-58)
  - Flamingo Foods Dirigible Project, 1951-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Ford Automobiles Dirigible Project (see also Box 14), 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 60-67)
  - Fort Pitt Beer Dirigible Project, ca. 1940s-1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Knickerbocker Beer Dirigible Project, ca. 1940s-1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - MGM (Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer) Dirigible Project, 1945-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - MGM, Dirigible Scrapbook 5 (see Box 10), 1945-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - MGM Duplicate Photographs, Dirigible Scrapbook 5, 1945-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Mobiloil/ Flying Red Horse Dirigible Project (see also Box 14), 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5-10)
  - Mobiloil/Flying Red Horse, Dirigible Scrapbook 6, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Mobiloil/Flying Red Horse, Dirigible Scrapbooks 7-8 (see Boxes 10, 14), 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Pfeiffer Beer Dirigible Project, ca. 1940s-1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - R & H Beer Dirigible Project (see also Box 14), ca. 1940s-1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Tydol Flying "A" Gasoline Dirigible Project, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15-16)
  - Tydol Flying "A" Gasoline, Dirigible Scrapbooks 9-11 (see Box 11), 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Tydol Flying "A" Gasoline Duplicate Photographs from Dirigible Scrapbooks, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Wonder Bread (see Box 14), 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19-27)
  - Oversized MGM (Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer), Dirigible Scrapbook 5, 1945-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Mobiloil/Flying Red Horse, Dirigible Scrapbook 8, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Tydol Flying "A" Gasoline, Dirigible Scrapbook 9, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Tydol Flying "A" Gasoline, Dirigible Scrapbook 10, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Tydol Flying "A" Gasoline, Dirigible Scrapbook 11, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Oversized General Petroleum/Mobiloil/Flying Red Horse, Dirigible Scrapbook 7, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Wonder Bread, Dirigible Scrapbook 12, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Dirigible Project Files, 1947-1949, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Drawings for Ford Automobile Advertisements
    Photograph of Ford Automobile Dirigible on Runway
    Photograph of Ford Automobile Dirigible in Flight
    Artwork for Knickerbocker Beer
    Poster for Knickerbocker Beer
    Photograph of Mobiloil Dirigible on Runway
    Poster of R & H Beer Dirigible
  - General Dirigible Scrapbook 1, 1946-1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - General Dirigible Scrapbook 2, 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - General Dirigible Scrapbook 3, 1947-1952; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - General Dirigible Scrapbook 4 General (includes a photograph of Elizabeth Taylor), 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Mobiloil, Dirigible Scrapbook 6 (includes a photograph of Elizabeth Taylor), 1947-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Urban Improvement Project Files, 1903-1992; Series 13; Archival Resource Key; (Box 9, 14, 28-32, OV 34; 2.2 linear feet)
  This series consists of photographs, a promotion book, clippings, miscellaneous printed material, 18 scrapbooks, and individual project files that document the development of Leigh's urban improvement projects involving both the construction design of new buildings and the lighting of prominent buildings in New York City and elsewhere. Project files typically contain photographs, printed materials, notes, floorplans, blueprints, and scattered letters. The 18 consecutively numbered scrapbooks document both individual project files and general multiple projects. Scrapbooks containing material concerning multiple products have been numbered first.
  Urban improvement project files are on reel 5848.
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Buildings in New York City, 1980-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Photograph File of Atlanta and New York, 1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 29-35)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1982-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Promotion Book of Clippings and Photographs, 1984-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 37-38)
  - General Urban Improvement, Scrapbook 1, 1957-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 39-46)
  - General Urban Improvement, Scrapbook 2 (see Box 28), 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - General Urban Improvement, Scrapbook 3 (see Box 14), 1963-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 48-50)
  - Airline Terminal on Sixth Avenue Project, 1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Bank of Tokyo Building (100 Broadway) Project, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Chrysler Corporation Building Project, ca. 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Claridge Building Project, ca. 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Claridge Building Project, Scrapbooks 4-6 (see Boxes 28-29), ca. 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Convention Center Project, 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - 42nd Street Renovation Project, ca. 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Four Corners (Fifth Avenue and 57th Street) Project, 1988-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Garment District Building, Scrapbook 7 (South side of 42nd Street) (see Box 29), 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Grand Central Station Project (see Also OV 34), 1946-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 60-62)
  - Helmsley Building (230 Park Avenue) Project, 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Helmsley Building, Scrapbook 8 (230 Park Avenue) Project (see Box 30), 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Pan Am Building Project, Scrapbook 9 (see Box 30), ca. 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Port Authority Project, Scrapbook 10 (see Box 31), ca. 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Times Building/Allied Chemical Building Project, 1903-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 67-69)
  - Times Building/Allied Chemical Building Project, Scrapbooks 11-12 (see Box 31), ca. 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Times Building/Allied Chemical Building Project, Scrapbooks 13-18 (see Box 32), April 1963-January 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 71-72)
  - Times Building/Allied Chemical Building Project, Printed Material, 1903-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 73-74)
  - Baltimore Urban Improvement Project, Maryland National Bank, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - City of Reno Urban Improvement Project (see also Box 32), ca. 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Cincinnati Urban Improvement Project File, Atrium I and II Lighting, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - New York City, Windowless Facade Between 45th and 46th Streets, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Oversize pages from Scrapbook 3, General Urban Improvement, 1963-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Oversize photographs of the Times and Allied Chemical Building Projects, 1903-circa 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Oversized General Urban Improvement, Scrapbook 2, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Claridge Building Project, Scrapbook 4, ca. 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Claridge Building Project, Scrapbook 5-6, ca. 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - Oversized Garment District Building (South side of 42nd Street) Project, Scrapbook 7, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Helmsley Building (230 Park Avenue) Project, Scrapbook 8, 1980-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Pan Am Building Project, Scrapbook 9, ca. 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Port Authority Project, Scrapbook 10, ca. 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Times Building/Allied Chemical Building Project, Scrapbooks 11-12, ca. 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - Oversized Times Building/Allied Chemical Building Project, Scrapbooks 13-18, April 1963-January 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 1-6)
  - Oversized Photographs from City of Reno Urban Improvement Project, ca. 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 7)